<resources>
    <string name="app_name">WatchPrivacyDog</string>
    <string name="app_desc">A tool that logs the stack trace of invocation of privacy functions</string>
    <string name="should_hook">Turn on Hook</string>
    <string name="show_invocation">Show Invocation</string>

    <string name="desc_get_address_network">get Mac Address of Network Adapter.</string>
    <string name="desc_get_address_bluetooth">get Mac Address of Bluetooth Adapter.</string>
    <string name="desc_get_running_app_processes">get a list of application processes that are running on the device.</string>
    <string name="desc_get_connection_info">get a list of application processes that are running on the device.</string>
    <string name="desc_get_host_address">Returns the IP address string in textual presentation.</string>
    <string name="desc_get_sensor_list">get the list of available sensors of a certain type. </string>
    <string name="desc_get_sim_serial_number">Returns the serial number of the SIM, if applicable. Return null if it is unavailable.</string>
    <string name="desc_get_meid">Returns the MEID (Mobile Equipment Identifier). Return null if MEID is not available.</string>
    <string name="desc_get_imei">Returns the IMEI (International Mobile Equipment Identity). Return null if IMEI is not available.</string>
    <string name="desc_get_serial">Gets the hardware serial number, if available.</string>
    <string name="desc_get_subscribe_id">Returns the unique subscriber ID, for example, the IMSI for a GSM phone. Return null if it is unavailable.</string>
    <string name="desc_get_device_id">Returns the unique device ID, for example, the IMEI for GSM and the MEID or ESN for CDMA phones. Return null if device ID is not available.</string>
    <string name="desc_get_android_id">It\'s a 64-bit number that should remain constant for the lifetime of a device. For apps that were installed prior to updating the device to a version of Android 8.0 (API level 26) or higher, the value of ANDROID_ID changes if the app is uninstalled and then reinstalled after the OTA. To preserve values across uninstalls after an OTA to Android 8.0 or higher, developers can use Key/Value Backup.</string>
    <string name="desc_get_installed_package">Return a List of all packages that are installed for the current user.</string>
    <string name="desc_get_query_intent_activities">Retrieve all activities that can be performed for the given intent.</string>
</resources>